# LUCAS PADILHA FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

### **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

- Praceta Verderena 9, Barreiro
- +351 912 015 235
- lucas\_padilha@icloud.com

# **ABOUT (PROFESSIONAL) ME**

I'm a person passionate for numbers, logical thinking and complex problems. All of my professional experience (in a lot of different fields) was based with this mindset and I'm pretty sure that kind of mind can change wherever environment that I am in.

### **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

### Le Wagon - Lisbon (Portugal)

Full-stack web development | 2019

- Ruby on Rails
- Heroku
- C#
- CSS3
- NET
- Javascript
- ASP.NET
- SQL
- node.js
- SQL Server
- Entity Framework

- Git Flow - Bootstrap - GitHub - jQuery

### FMU FISP - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

Civil Engineering | Feb 2012 . Jan 2015

- Numerical calculation
- Structural calculation
- Physics
- Mathematics

### CNA - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

English Course | Jan 2009 - Dec 2011

# **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese | ••••••••
English | •••••••

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Software Developer**

Inspire IT Portugal | Jan 2020 - Present (Portugal)

- Development in full-stack (C#, .NET, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript)
- SQL Server for database management
- Visual Studio for development

The project that I am in, is GLLG, a platform about education management in Perú. Most of the time, I develop the backend in C# and .NET, using entity framework (is changing to Dapper), and the front-end I am doing with ASP.NET, using HTML and CSS too, and jQuery.

We use JIRA to project management, using Kanban methodology and bitbucket as coding management platform.

### **Logistics and Warehouse's Manager**

Brodheim Group | Jul 2017 - Oct 2019 (Portugal)

- Merchandise management
- Partial and general inventories
- Logistical control between chain stores
- Contacts with suppliers

### **Math and Physics teacher**

Study Center Primavera | Jan 2017 - Jul 2017

- Explanations and classes, in mathematics and physics, for students from the 1st to the 12th grade.

### **Team Coordinator**

Thousand Solutions | Mar 2016 - Jan 2017 (Portugal)

- Direct customer acquisition for energy business contracts
- Manage team for that same function
- Lead daily morning meetings

### Salesperson and Sub-manager

Levi Strauss & CO | Jan 2014 - Dec 2015 (Brazil)

- Team management
- Sale of products to the public

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

### **WALD PROJECT**

- Co-founder of WALD Project, a software that creates and configure a RailsApp from scratch, just with the visual schema from database.

In that project, I used JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3 to build the public pages (404, 500), alerts, confirmations and buttons; bootstrap for default designs changing just specific layouts with CSS; GitHub API for omniauth authentication; Heroku for deployment in a server; and PostgreSQL for our relational database; Ruby on Rails for back-end, creating a default template and using interpolation for each option choose by user.

Ch	eck-us on:
	waldproject.com

### **RABBIT**

- Rabbit is a website that simulates AirBnb (giant website that is based on RoR), the site have the same AirBnb functions, rent an animal - in our case - , have the animal card in map (using API from mapbox), different type of user (with authentication for admin and normal user, animations...

In that project, I used HTML5 and CSS3 (with bootstrap also) for the pages design, JavaScript for alerts animations, drag and drop for weekly top5, Heroku to deploy on a host service, SQLite3 for the database and Ruby on Rails for all the back-end.

$\sim 1$		1			
( 'h	iec	lν_'	110	$\alpha$ r	1

☐ https://pet-shop-boys-9000.herokuapp.com/